EKATERINA YARMOSHUK

POSITION

Middle systems analyst

CONTACT INFORMATION

E-MAIL: katerina.tatarevich@gmail.com | PHONE: +375 25 909 10 61

SKYPE: katrin.tatarevich | LINKEDIN: linkedin.com

ABOUT

Experienced systems analyst with skills in business requirements analysis, identifying development defects, and requirements defects. Apart from work, I dedicate time to learning frontend development and interacting with backend systems. I have gained experience working with HTML, CSS (including preprocessors like SASS, SCSS), and JavaScript. My projects you can find here. The profession of a systems analyst appeals to me due to its ability to see the bigger picture of a system. I deeply immerse myself in both the technical and business aspects of projects.

SKILLS

- UML
- OOP
- REST
- Jira, Confluence
- MySQL, PostgreSQL

- Git
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS (preprocessors SASS, SCSS)
- ReactJS

English level: Intermediate (B1)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nov 2021 - Febr 2022 - Internship, iTechArt Group

Jun 2021 - Sept 2021 - Development of web applications on JavaScript, Educational Center for Programming and High Tech (IT-Academy)

Project: the game "The Rocket Wars"

Project description: the game "The Rocket Wars" is my final project as a student of IT-Academy.

Sept 2020 - Des 2020 - Development of website on ReactJS, Vlad Basin's Online course (EPAM)

Nov 2014 - Aug 2017 – CRM Oracle Siebel System Analyst (3rd line of support), **Sberbank-Technology** Main responsibilities:

- CRM incident analytics;
- Analysis of the interaction with other banking systems;
- Identification of development defects;
- · Identification of requirements defects;
- Cooperation with developers, CRM users;
- Requirements description for correcting defective data

Nov 2012 - Nov 2014 - Financial Specialist (Business Analyst), life:) Belarus (Turkcell Group) Main responsibilities:

• Coordination and implementation of the budgeting project, Cash Flow;

- The budgeting module settings;
- Management/support of information databases in ERP Oracle E-Business Suite;
- Creating of business procedures and instructions;
- Financial modules support (General Ledger, Payables Manager, Receivers Manager, Cash Management, Assets)

Jan 2012-Jun2012 - Finance Accountant, KiT Conculting Agency

Main responsibilities:

- Interaction with the Customer regarding business issues
- Preparation of internal documentation
- Currency distribution, payments transfer

EDUCATION

Jun 2021 - Sept 2021 - Educational Center for Programming and High Tech (IT-Academy)

Course: Development of web applications on JavaScript (Certificate);

Sept 2020 - Des 2020 - Vlad Basin's Online course (EPAM)

Course: Foundation of Web Development (HTML, CSS (preprocessor SASS, SCSS), JavaScript, ReactJS);

2014 – Oracle Apps Forum 2014

The main topics of the forum: Siebel CRM, project management in Oracle ERP, integrated budgeting, controlling and procurement processes;

2013 - ERP Team FA integration training

Topic: system administration;

2007-2012 - Belarusian National Technical University

Degree Name: High School Diploma Specialization: Business administration

Екатерина Ярмошук

Должность

Системный аналитик

Контактная информация

E-MAIL: katerina.tatarevich@gmail.com | PHONE: +375 25 909 10 61

SKYPE: katrin.tatarevich | LINKEDIN: linkedin.com

О себе

Опытный системный аналитик с навыками в анализе бизнес-требований, выявлении дефектов разработки и дефектов требований. Кроме работы, уделяю время изучению frontend разработки и взаимодействия с backend. Приобрела опыт работы с HTML, CSS (включая препроцессоры SASS, SCSS) и JavaScript. Список моих проектов можно посмотреть здесь. Профессия системного аналитика привлекает меня своим целостным подходом. Я глубоко погружаюсь и в техническую, и бизнес-стороны проектов.

Навыки

- UML
- ООП
- REST
- Jira, Confluence
- MySQL, PostgreSQL
- Git

- Draw.io
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS (препроцессор SASS, SCSS)
- ReactJS

Уровень английского языка: Intermediate (B1)

Опыт работы

Ноябрь 2021 – февраль 2022 – Стажировка, iTechArt Group

Июнь 2021 - сентябрь 2021 - Разработка веб-приложений на JavaScript, **Образовательный центр программирования и высоких технологий (IT-Academy) Проект:** игра <u>"The Rocket Wars"</u>

Сентиябрь 2020 - декабрь 2020 - Разработка веб-сайта на ReactJS, **Онлайн-курс Влада Басина** (**EPAM**)

Ноябрь 2014 - август 2017 — Системный аналитик (3-я линия поддержки) CRM Oracle Siebel, **ООО** "Сбербанк-Технологии"

Основные обязанности:

- Анализ инцидентов в CRM;
- Анализ процессов взаимодействия с другими банковскими системами;
- Выявление дефектов разработки;
- Выявление дефектов требований;
- Сотрудничество с разработчиками, пользователями СРМ;
- Описание требований по исправлению дефектных данных;

Ноябрь 2012 - ноябрь 2014 – Специалист финансового департамента (Бизнес аналитик), **life:)** (3AO БеСТ)

Основные обязанности:

- Координация и внедрение проекта бюджетирования, Cash Flow;
- Контроль правильности и точности данных, загружаемых в систему;
- Поддержка и управление информационных баз данных в ERP Oracle E-Business Suite;
- Координация работы Отдела бухгалтерского учета и планирования с отделом МСФО (сбор и анализ требований пользователей, согласование с Заказчиком действий в ERP, урегулирование разногласий между участниками процесса);
- Тестирование системы при внедрении новых бизнес-процессов и доработки уже существующих;
- Поддержка и консультирование пользователей в процессе их работы;
- Создание, написание бизнес-процедур и инструкций;
- Поддержка финансовых модулей (General Ledger, Payables Manager, Receivables Manager, Cash Management, Assets);

Январь 2012 - июнь 2012 — финансовый специалист, **консалтинговое бюро "КиТ"** Основные обязанности:

- Взаимодействие с Заказчиком относительно вопросов ведения бизнеса;
- Составление внутренней документации, бизнес-процессов;
- Работа с клиент банком (распределение валюты, проведение платежей, выгрузки из банка, загрузка данных в 1С);

Образование

Июнь 2021 - Сентябрь 2021 — Образовательный центр программирования и высоких технологий (IT-Academy)

Название курса: Разработка веб-приложений на JavaScript (Certificate);

Сентябрь 2020 - декабрь 2020 - Онлайн-курс Влада Басина (ЕРАМ)

Название курса: Основы веб разработки (HTML, CSS, препроцессор SASS, SCSS, JavaScript, ReactJS);

2014 - Oracle Apps Forum 2014

Основные темы форума: Siebel CRM, управление проектами в Oracle ERP, интегрированные процессы бюджетирования, контроллинга и закупок;

2013 - ERP Team FA integration training

Тема: системное администрование;

2007-2012 - Белорусский национальный технический университет

Образование: высшее;

Специальность: бизнес-администрирование;